proarticles.co.uk 2016-12-27

# Privacy policy - BTC Diamond

Almaz Invest is well-informed that your privacy is important to you, and we want you to know that it is important to us too. We created this Privacy Policy to explain the types of information we collect through our Web sites and the various social networking platforms that we use (hereinafter referred to as the “Site”). This Privacy Policy describes how we will use, disclose and protect  
this information once it is collected, and how you can opt-out of some of our uses of your information.

Personal information of Users/Customers is processed in compliance with the Law of Estonia “On personal data” and in accordance with the present Privacy Policy.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on the Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name; employer name; day and month of birth;  
postal addresses; e-mail addresses; telephone numbers; fax numbers; wireless device addresses (including text message addresses); photograph; gender; credit card and other payment information. Users may, however, visit the Site anonymously. We will collect  
personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply  
personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with the the Almaz Invest websites http://www.btcdiamond.com and https://app.btcdiamond.com (the “Site”). Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to the Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

The Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Almaz Invest may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

**Social networking**

We maintain presence on several social networking and blogging platforms, and we also incorporate some third party social networking features onto the Site. Through these platforms and features, we receive some Personal Information and some Site Usage Information about you, and this Privacy Policy applies to that information as well. In addition, third party social networking platforms and blogging platforms have their own privacy policies which explain how the third parties that provide them will use and protect  
your information.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on the Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on the Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to the Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Almaz Invest may modify this privacy at any time upon posting notice on the Web Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using the Site, you signify your acceptance of this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
